[Music]
In the name of God, webinar number 4L, group A, is at
my service in order. Please
excuse me for number 11. Mr. Reza. Hello again.
Hello guys. No, I have no questions. Mr. Reza. I have
no questions about the decisions. No, I have no questions.
For now, let's move on. Insha Allah. The
composition. Maybe I will have a question.
This is what you had in mind before.
About this type of view of DPs. Yes,
by the way, I only do DPs, as you
said. DPs and Ss. And these two others.
Yes, of course, there
is another type of DP, which is this. Now, in
addition to my special DPs, I will draw them with Antid. Please
serve you.
Then the
table breaks. CPA.
Well done. This is my DPA trend. If yes, yes,
I have this trend line that breaks. Here, I have a DP. Of
course, there is also this here that D does not go ahead.
This kink that ends with a sipid.
Here, I am here. Kin that goes with a sipid. That
DP that breaks this falls below this trend line.
Now, Mr. Reza.  As you say, I do
n't know what it is called, but I trade these,
this and this last one that stays here
before Else, this is something in the middle, one of them is the
first one, one of them is in the middle, one of them is the one that goes down Else goes down
here if I
have a dip here if you consider this a compression
here there is a decision to break it
that you will work on but what you are
saying here has a category that
this is used for this top, this
bottom itself is used for this, that is, when the whole thing
falls here and hits, it
itself must give it a retracement. Now let me
talk about compression, I will come back and put it
in there because compression itself needs a
series of inflows and outflows and complements a
separate topic, a separate course. The discussion of compression,
well, in your journal, tell me, Ipi.
Now, the reality is that what I have
experienced now and during this time I have worked with my art
has a fluidity, that is, it is not certain
that this is a dip sometimes.  It comes and hits it.
Sometimes it's something fluid that you
can't be sure about. It's definitely a dip.
Sometimes it comes and hits something below the dip. Then, for example, according to
some friends who
say that when the market ended, it moved
from behind, from left to right, from here to there. I
can find an explanation for that. But in the live market, there is
no certainty
about the trade of that dip, let's say 100. Now, this is even the
left shoulder, Mr. Reza. Sometimes you see that the
left shoulder that you put is a beautiful dip. It's both an
original swap and a left shoulder swap. From there, you see that it
comes down, something else. I'm
exaggerating now, but I combine it with the sessions.
For example, I say that this DP created in this session is
likely to be undermined by the DP
created in the Asia session.
For example, I am going to do these things empirically, that is, based
on my own experience, I wrote these in the past one or two
years, I kept them, I am mixing them into this
story, but right now, what
you taught was smooth and simple,
no more. Now, I don't have any specific questions.
Yes, your report writing shows that you had a very special
way of
looking at things. It was part of the report writing process,
both the report writing and your own
exercises were
not corrective. This is in this discussion
and almost all of those points. Now, some
decisions are made in order to be criticized,
and basically, the certainty that you are talking about is
for its preservation. But what is
important is that decisions are based on the positions of the
Wolloeh Hai Lu
himself,
if it
is a result or a result or a result of criticism, this decision
that is made here will be different for its failure.
That is, we should not look at everything at once, look at it at once,
that is, we should put these cases in a different category.
Then we will say
whether  A low or a high is a
result of a reaction or they themselves were violated that the
decision was made, that is, it was broken, that in return, what
end will it have, the Ingolf session will end,
all this is a
gel in the Ingolf session, it is
told to you like this and along with these arrows, which is the only thing
left for this topic,
God willing. But well, Mr. Reza, I have something to
tell you, there is something that all of us,
art and work, are caught up in. This
Ingolf story, which I can almost say is slowly
becoming hopeless at
finding it, that I am definitely deleting this, this, this story,
this story, in my mind, and
now the reality is that this Golf is
really very difficult to recognize. Really, this,
this Golf, some, this Golf, sometimes you see it, it
comes much further, it shoots, hey, you are
waiting down, for example, this story of gold, for example,
yesterday, the day before yesterday, it went up so high that it
found a small kink there, from
there, I was hitting
every kink of your left shoulder from there.  The
higher structure, hey, I made a trade, hey, I made a trade, D to S3, you
made a mistake, when you
realize this, look at
these arrows, when you realize something,
this is the one, when it is hit on its back, you
will not come to this structure itself, look for the sell
because this is the one behind it, this is the one you will
learn at least in this course, no,
Mr. Reza, if you press it, there is a lift from the left,
throw it,
this is the roof, it will be a handle, that is, you, yes, for
example, here, when I made a move, there was
a D to kink from above here, I
made a Kinga Trade on it, of course, it was
compensated on the previous MPL, the last one I had taken, that is, the
one that was above here,
I was able to compensate, now I can close without loss,
but well, from here, that move that I made
could have been behind this, I said, this is liquidity,
now it may not have anything to do with the discussion,
but I said, this is the liquidity kink of this story,
this is my move here, it should be hit on its back, D to
kink, which was very small, I said, okay  This is a criticism
of appreciation and this is the beauty of it, as the saying goes, it
should be hit on the back. It is Asia's massage.
Here I should be able to get one, for example, at least one one-
two-one-three. The reality is
this, but when it went from that high, came back and
from there it gave such a retracement and came down.
For me, for example, I say, God,
what else should I do? Leave it alone. I will delete it
from my trading story altogether because I
can't find it at all. I find it 40 times.
60 times it puts my hand in the walnut shell. I hope God will be
able to optimize it together. God will be able to
optimize this. Please,
thank you. Please, Mr. Rahimzad, please,
Mr. Reza, I'm sorry. I think it's done now.
Saddam is coming. Yes, yes, please. Well, I was just asking. I
just had a question about this.
If I can, please let me draw it. Yes,
Mr. Reza. I mean, if he comes under
this quinco, go back to this left, which
I pulled a little lower here.
I mean this left now.  If it
then comes back here, we will
no longer have a trading plan when it comes from above and below. That's right,
you are saying that based on this, you are saying that if
we have a decision here, this is the decision to hit
this shoulder, then this is the decision to
break this decision. Then when it comes back, another way,
then it comes down, for example, it hits the bottom. Then it
comes back to inking. We will
no longer have a trading plan.
That's right, what you are saying is right. But if it
comes in the form of a face after hitting this, it should be consumed. It
usually doesn't have a special quality.
But sometimes, this left shoulder with this
plate
has a reason that in the future, in my big structure,
after hitting this low, it will work here
.  Ah, now it's time for him to
create his own perspective.  That means you have an area on the left that is
behind it, and then
below it, there is an area that is below it.   The fact
that it can be done in two directions is useful at that time
.  Now let's come to this golf.
About it, oh, this is the priority of this golf.
This is
another thing. You asked Mr. Reza about the
Bitcoin chart. I think you said why, for
example, what is your reason for saying that, for example, on this DP
you
[music]
will have a trading program.
Let's bring the Bitcoin chart. Just see if I understand the matter. That's all I
mean. Tell me, let me delete this entry.
Yes, well, tell me exactly where it was. I think how
many minutes is the time of this time, Mr. Reza. It's 4
hours.
That time was 4 hours. At
your service.
Well,
a little bit to the left. We asked a question. You said
why, I think, on that bit, come to that
chart. There's nothing here. It's gone.
Why was it here? I think
it's not.
This was Mr. Reza. I
think you said, why is this important to you? That's
right.
You said, why is this DP important to you?
Well, I said one because it was a stanari who
went and hit that low levy. Then here, sir, he has a left
because of the one that
fell. Can you give me one?  One of the reasons why this
DP is important is
this left, yes, well, what did this left do that
could be important? No, it didn't do anything.
Because of that, it couldn't. Yes,
if it worked, you mean that it was
ignored. I mean, this is the DP.
This was the tip that I
just marked. This was the DP
for the break. This was the DP for the
break. Yes, this was the
DP. Then you said why this is
important to you. I said because I only gave one
reason. One of the reasons was that
this came. This important snare. It was decided
for him. This important snare. Because he went
down. Then another reason could
be this left that didn't work here. And
this method was formed. This picture.
No, it's not this. No, it's not this. I'll give you the same situation
now. But if I explain later,
you
have this Kinko here in this area. Right, yes, it's right.
This hit the back. The price. Well, the
price hit here.
In this area, it hit the king.
Then it hit here.  What
happened?
You saw that until that minute, both sides were
hit by this. Well, whenever it hits,
this has priority over this. For now, no, no,
first up, then down. When it
crosses the top, it will
come for this low. No, wait. This low
code will be activated when its high is removed.
That is, when the price crosses these highs, it
should come to remove this low.
That is, this low will go behind it, then it will go under it,
then when it crosses the top, it will come to remove
this low
.
This is the limit,
now
the kink
here is getting smaller.  Can you do this here? Yes,
this with this.
So, did you understand this?  Yes, yes, completely.
Please, take a look at my journal. If
you sent me a workout, then the next person, please, did
you send it this week? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, okay.
I said in my journal. Your workout is great. Thank you. I'll raise your hand.
Please. Good evening, number 10.
Mr. Mardani.
Hello, Mr. Reza. I hope you are well.
Hello, Mr. Mardani. Thank you.
Mr. Reza. I just had a previous meeting. The
meeting we had was about DPs. Then my
first question is, do we trade DPs
or do we get an opinion from them? That is,
if he comes to hit his back or, I don't know,
come. For example, now, this golfer. Both.
Both.
For example, if first, for example, we come to analyze
or, if not, I'll sit in. Mr. Reza. For example, I'll share my
chart. For
example, let me say this same opinion with you. Yes, this
Mr. Abbasio, let him come in. He's gone to sleep.
This whole session is over. This person
doesn't get his name right. Yes, please.
For example, when we come into the chart, we'll
We take what we have to
do now, the things we
learned, for example, if this is the
market here, we will actually
draw one SNR for example here, then we say,
well, where is this SR actually drawn here,
then for example, we say, King before that, if this
is here, for example, there is a DP
for us, is it right?
Then now,
we will come and check this in the current market
or not, we will come in advance. I
mean, I want to make my point of view from now on, from the
basics, like you, sir, when I
come and sit behind the system, what should I look at, what should I pay
attention to, so that I can come and trade, for example, you know
what I'm saying, or no, for
example, this is the current market, no, I have to
come from here, for example, I have to come to come
here
to understand these, or for example, this SA, well, that
SR, it doesn't matter at all, what is this Sweetland
Euro, for example, now, take your time in the
30s,
one-day, two-day, what kind of format do you use?
Basically I
put it like this I don't know
TG in another country's language German
ah yes you can do one for example daily or
do 4 hours
for example these four hours you were in Austria right
Austrians Germany in our language I
understand well yes look now in the
daily time frame is good you always have to
see where the market is going in the upper time frame first let's
come this way ah
well look in the future you always
look at the upper structure first after the
upper structure view for medicine
well first say for example well this is a low that
the price has now
gone up one high where did these highs go you
have to look at all these one highs
here there was a decision this decision was
ignored in the return right right
when they were broken they were ignored
so this this this when you draw white on
them price comes and breaks this when
allowed to trade its return this when it
crosses this low so when the return this low is crossed
the price returns to the ignored area meaning
here this white yes this is after you if
after  If the price breaks back into this
area and you have traded and stopped out,
when the bullish signal hits, you will come back
here again. Take this short to the bottom, that
is, take the sell signal to the lower area. This is for
this two-day DP and
Ignore topic that
was discussed in this meeting, or was it just a decision?   It was
just a decision, this lack of decision, now in the
next meeting, well, now that's an example, the
next example that we'll follow, for example, well,
again,
first we have to learn, for example, that Lu and
Hayamun in the next meetings, do they have
a
change of perspective, that these kings that
exist can
help us, for example, to continue the path or change the perspective.  Now,
if we have this low here, when
the price comes to hit the back of this area, that is, it
comes to hit this low, then a
violation has happened to us. This violation is delayed in the chapter
due to the failure of this low or what happened to
this low.
Because the price comes to hit the back of the box first
and the low has come to fail. Let's stick these
together. These decisions create my path for me.
When it hits this low again,
for example, the expectations for one, that is,
if it hits this low again, for example, it has come here now, it
may come back and hit this low
again. Even this and this, why should it hit
this low? You will learn what this low did first,
what it did, what it did.
Basically, did the next low reach its target or
not? It was just a confirmation of this low.
Oh, sorry. You have to put all of this
together. Well, when you put this next to that,
you will understand whether this low will be hit after hitting
this low or not. These all say that you will understand.
You will understand this like this for the chart.
Come to the point, we'll put everything
together, we'll understand, but in the end you'll put everything together, yeah,
this is it, excuse me, in the
words this is it, this is it, excuse me, this is it, or
these, it's important to us that these, for example, where to
eat in these parts, right?  Yes, yes,
where do these go? These become important to us in such a way
that we can make decisions about
what to do. What to do? You have to
put these together. Look at the
position of this white kink that I drew.
Or, now, if this position is appropriate,
why is it appropriate? This is a question that
you have to answer by looking at these.
Well, because, for example, there was a break here before, there was a
king. We say, "DP." Well, this
DP is the result. Is there an area here that,
when you come and say, what created this low?
This king and this next to Hemming,
this break. So, this can be a decision
for this. So, you can have a cell perspective method to
send the price to the lower areas.
Where are these lower areas? You come back and say,
what broke this low? You have to find the decision that broke this low.
This can send the price
to the decision that you formed in the opposite way,
which is called a decision-making decision.
I'll draw a schematic here so it fits you
.  For example, you have a king here, the
price has come and
gone,
and here you have a low, and this becomes a low
in return. This is ignored. Yes, so
the price from here to the higher area can
continue to move up to here. Well, this is its
position in
such a way that it can hold once, it can
send it to the edge of this price, then at the
edge of this. Now, to find out what this is
because it is ignored, that is,
if there was a decision here that this decision was
made in the opposite way and the term ignore is used in it.
And yes,
what are you doing here?  You close most of your trades with
high volume.  Why do you say that?  Because the
red zone is an
ignored zone, the boss can usually
hit a higher one and this king will be broken.
So here you have to put a decision of indecision, an
ingolf, an FO, a pause and a delay
together so that you can decide for that king
that you want to have an analytical and trading approach. Okay, so I
understand. Then Mr. Reza,
another question about the left. Now, the left shoulder. For example,
if you pay attention to the
example here, we can say that, okay, for example,
this is our left. This is not, we can't
say, no, not only now, you can see it as a
pattern,
but the left itself is also
selected based on a framework. That is, you
can't take every left as saying,
this has a left shoulder. Maybe, aha. So, for
example, here, here, we can't even take it. Maybe,
or no, aha. Look, zoom back a little.
No.
[Music]
[Applause]
So, you want to choose a left shoulder from these lines here
and explain
the reason.  The thing is,
those lows that I want to make a shoulder
for the next lows, for example, here this
low goes, it should go behind this area, it hits this area,
and so to speak, you become empty,
in this area, you
become empty, and then it comes under
this area, it hits, now that it comes back up,
this low is important because it has created a perspective,
which I will explain more in the left,
this is important here, so basically, this
low is because it has created a perspective and everyone is buying,
then liquidity is created under it, we come from this, we draw
a left shoulder, here it becomes a
level, it means that that left shoulder is somehow important,
what gigabytes it has created, it means that it has to be a
result, something that we can say,
this left shoulder is nothing for now, that left
must have created a perspective, it has created a series of empty, it has
created a series of empty perspective here, we said, okay,
then it came under it, now this can
work for us, yes, okay, Mr. Reza  Just one
more thing, it's over, like, okay,
okay, for example, in the high time, there's a lot of work,
so we can
figure this out later in the low time.
This is related to your skill.  I
can't guarantee that you will be successful in
one minute.  You, let me give you 5
minutes and look at this. You will
notice a frame. Now, if it is above the daily time,
how many time frames is it?
Yes, we have several time frames above the daily time frame. We can put
two together,
one weekly, and actually monthly. Yes, that's good. So
if you're working on the daily, you
want to put two fractals together here.
If you're working below the daily time frame, how many fractals should you
put together? Go for the 4-hour fractal, you'll also go for the
1-hour fractal,
go for the 15-minute and 5-minute, and that 1-minute one, that's it.
If you have the ability to
put these together, you can also deal with the structures in the 1-minute one.
But if you don't have the ability, you'll raise
your structure time frame higher and lower your time frame to optimize
your entry.
[Music]
Okay, I get it.  So it's better to have a
higher time limit.  In order to
understand a trend during the week, first
look at the daily, then the weekly, then the 4-hour and
1-hour charts, respectively, so that you
can make your guesses
and find areas to trade during the week. Then, the
15-minute structure is suitable or 5-minute is suitable for you to
optimize the entry area. Yes, Mr.
Reza says in the above time frame, for example, it wants to fall.
We will find a king zone in 5 minutes,
something that we can enter in.
For example, now you think, tomorrow you
want this, come here, so you expect
some areas to be hit. You come
here. You find an area that when it
is hit below, meaning a break, you wait for a retracement to the
area here and act for the lower area.
This is because it is a weekly trend. Yes, only
when you reach the weekend area do you go
here?  So you don't expect the
price to go lower here.  Oh, so next week you're
looking for
structures that show the price, it wants to
come back, that's right, okay, I
understand, your hand is
broken, I
'm here now, Mr. Reza, your hand doesn't hurt,
thank you very much for your explanation,
please, so the
next person is
Amir, at your service, Mr. Reza. A question
I had was that in these kinks that did
n't have a kink break, in one of the examples, it did
n't work when I came back. Does this swap work or did
I misunderstand?  No no no mistake if
our king breaks see something now good you said
see about king breaks is that we
bring your annotate like this
we have a
if we have a levy here most of the time this is
in the state what is a low what is a high now I m
example bearish and bullish whichever you were comfortable
tell me I will hit
we have a low now the price is going with a here
area or one behind an area
this low means it starts from here
goes here and then comes one breaks this
means here does a liquidity gathering
or we have a tight range
the price comes here and breaks this and on the way
back goes up means that kink is ignored in two
cases
this kink means a beat is
broken here it does not take time to
make kink break in this in the form of a single candlestick
here it is hit in succession it goes up and
goes in the larger structure the price returns to
this area this area which was now in
red returns here
I said that in the video limited if  In the form of a single
candle, this upper edge is suitable for entry,
but you should always put the stop loss here, or
if you want to optimize it, you should go
inside
and see this retracement position, for example, the
range that I am talking about.
Imagine in your mind that this low has broken, the low that
existed here has come down, these highs
that have broken here, the king that has now
existed in the small time frame that has overcome this, so I will
enter a little lower, the
spread above this, and the stop loss here.
If all conditions are OK, this single candle that
falls here is for optimizing the art,
but if someone wants to study this and
says no, put the stop loss below this, it is convenient. That is, the most
correct thing is to put the stop below this, and these, for
example, to optimize here, here is
the stop loss here, it should continue to give the Messiah.
In most of these, this situation occurs here because
liquidity accumulates here and the market comes and hits
this view below this liquidity, then it
goes back up, this king does not have the opportunity to
make a way.  When it comes back, they need a
few things to make it fit better
or be a trading setup. For someone who
wants to trade on this basis, for example, consider a
few points when the price
breaks this area upwards.
One that has momentum here
usually works much better in the candlestick that is now falling as a single
candle.
These work much better and can be
counted on in the reversals. Now, if it does
n't work here again, it goes down somewhere and it doesn't
work at all. So where did it
fail here? Where did you see this?
That session that you provided a video of. This is one
of the examples. Now, maybe I misunderstood.
This reversal didn't work. Then the swap was held.
But the price now. I will send it exactly
later in the journal. Yes, maybe or I said it wrong.
Yes, for example, send it so that I can correct it if there is anything.
Another question, I don't know if it is
relevant now or not. In this DPI model 2 and
3, which is obtained, it is lost or the same type.  They are the ones
that form in these areas before
that DP forms. We are waiting for a trade
based on whether there is a pattern there or
we already have a signal there, like,
yes, exactly, we are expecting it. Many are expecting this
there
in that area. Since the price is coming back from above,
many are expecting to
trade here.  That is, I am waiting in this area for,
for example, in this example, I am waiting for the
opposite to happen and it breaks,
and when it breaks, it returns
to this area, now you should trade
downwards.
First, here is the view. Yes, there is a view.
This is the basic view. Then, when
it comes here, it decides
not to respect this. When it comes back, it can be
traded. And this is itself. Now, if you want to be more
precise, let's
look at this area. Let's
find this kink. First, this
soup should be made so that these can make a bottom together.
When they make a bottom, it will be nice to
calculate them. Now, I didn't give the examples in this one.
Oh, I fell out because of that.
Now, the examples I gave in that session.
If it wasn't enough, then I can give an example for him in the next session. He
knows a lot about
the situation of another zone. There are areas where there are expectations
for that kink and vice versa.
It can hold the price.
And this is for an
open question. If you have any, please tell me.
If it was, now I will give you the DPR.
Otherwise, it seems like it. Thank you very much. Please, I will
sacrifice in the name of God. Greetings and good time. I
am at your service, dear friends and companions. We are
very happy to be here with the new trading
course of the Zeus Group.  We are with you. This
course is published in its entirety in a dedicated playlist
with the same name on Zeus' official YouTube page at
Zeus Forex Channel, and all
sessions can be viewed in order from the first episode
.  In this course, you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically.  After watching each session, you can
practice and then watch 6
short half-hour sessions of troubleshooting by friends
who participated in the round to
get a better understanding of the material. After that,
enter the next teaching session. To communicate
directly with us and use the troubleshooting plans,
simply send a message to the Telegram ID of Zeus Group
Underline of this admin and stay in touch with us
.  Wishing you all success in your
trading career, my dears.
[Music]